Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Yami and Asta were locked in a desperate battle against Licht, their defeat all but certain.
Take your last breath, Yami, superhero. Engaging life magic, ray of divine punishment.
And we're dead.
But then, some unexpected help arrived.
He came back?
Go, mirror magic! Full reflection!
Ghosh's spell reflected Licht's attack back at its caster, saving the magic knights.
Your magic might be fast, and powerful, but mirror will always reflect light.
It was a close call, but the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun was finally defeated.
He's finally defeated.
He's then defeated!
He said, let's Marie,
We'll be right back.
You dragged your scrawny butt back, and that you brought a fancy new spell with you.
Captain, you made me who I am today. Thank you. I owe you everything.
Oh, is that so? Then I get all the credit for beating the Light Mage, right?
What kind of sense does that make?
Ghosh did everything while you just stood there!
Shut it!
So you think since you beat Skinny Bones, you can just say whatever you want now, huh?
Hey, the important thing is that everybody did his best. There's no need for violence.
Oh yeah? What'd you do?
Excuse me? It was my facial magic that made it all possible!
No one cares. Now send me back to Marie.
All right, I've had it. I am your superior!
Well, my angel, your big brother did it.
And soon, you'll be in my arms, hugging me tight, sweet Marie.
Well, let's go.
I am your superior.
Well, anyway, I told you I only had one more spell in me.
Nobody's leaving this cave until my magic recovers.
Don't you?
Me?
Marie should never be kept waiting.
Here, I thought he couldn't get any more useless.
Now you're just being mean.
So much for that super powerful spell of yours, line face.
Guess your magic has more than one natural enemy.
Nice try, though.
I'm sorry.
I should never have hurt you.
Me? What are you talking about?
Oh, didn't know you guys were friends or I wouldn't have beat him up.
Of course I'm not friends with this monster.
One day, you'll understand.
I don't think I'll ever understand you and your little minions,
but we'll be hauling you back to headquarters anyway.
You can tell us all about the Eye of the Midnight Sun when we get there.
At last, the King of Overly Serious People has been avenged.
May he rest in peace now.
But he's not dead yet, sir!
Do we have to worry about every little detail?
Jeez!
Little detail?
Okay now, let's see here.
We've got a binding spell somewhere.
Just gotta find it.
Right, here it is.
Go Dark Restraints.
We should have gotten some reinforcements by now.
Where is everybody?
Ah!
Well, Miss Black Bull,
I'm happy to report that I informed your captain about the situation ages ago.
You went to the hideout?
It was positively awful.
He wouldn't listen to a word I said.
Okay, so what did Captain Yami do?
Probably headed out soon after that.
Ha ha!
What?
But where did he go?
He hasn't shown up here.
Huh?
Luca.
Marco.
Huh?
Ah!
Good thing it's about shift change.
I've earned myself some rest.
The captain usually wakes up around now,
and he'll be expecting a report.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
How about I tear you in two?
Hee hee!
I'd much rather skip that part.
Captain Jack's a scary man.
Mommy!
Oh, thank goodness.
I was so scared.
You're okay now, sweetie.
Don't worry.
There, there.
Everything will be all right now.
The village children.
They're back,
and no one looks hurt.
The magic knights came and saved us.
You're the one who told them we needed help.
Thank you.
Oh, sure.
It's the magic knights' duty to protect the people, after all.
And all I did was call headquarters.
They went straight there instead of stopping by the village first.
Why did they leave me behind?
Sister Teresa helped, too!
You should have seen the awesome spells she did!
If there was this mean guy who got turned into bed,
it was really scary.
Where are Luca and Marco?
Did they not make it back with you?
What about Asta and Ghosh?
I don't see any other magic knights for that matter.
Papa, Papa, Papa, Papa.
Papa.
Hosta!
Luca!
Marco!
Big sense!
Oh!
Thank goodness!
You're back!
I was so scared!
What happened to Sister Teresa?
Is she going to be okay?
Don't you worry about me now.
I'll be on my feet in no time.
I've got at least another hundred years in me.
Thank you.
I don't know how we'll ever repay you for bringing them back to us.
You're welcome, but I certainly didn't do it alone.
Those boys were...
Please, Sister.
No more talking.
That robe.
Oh, it's Asta's, but he let me borrow it.
He said as long as I wore it, I wouldn't be scared, and he was totally right.
I had so much courage, I didn't even cry.
Good job.
I'm proud of you.
And Asta, he came back with you, didn't he?
He stayed behind in the cave.
What?
He's still there.
The battle isn't over yet.
Yes, another one showed up.
Sister.
Another one?
A mage named Ligt.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun's leader.
And that's who Asta's still fighting?
He's there with a man named Captain Yami, and...
My brother went to help too.
A man who uses spatial magic took him.
I know they're gonna be fine.
There's nothing my big brother can't do.
Yes, I'm sure you're right.
They'll be just fine.
All four of them are strong.
They'll come back after they've defeated him.
Oh.
Fenral and Ghosh, too.
If they were here in town, they could have taken me to Asta.
I mean, not that it's all about him.
I'm not worried about Asta or anything.
Magic Knights should stick together.
It's the principle of the thing.
Let it go.
Okay, and who are you?
Well, um...
It's kind of a long story.
Can we get out of here already?
No.
You'll have to wait a little longer.
Like I said, it's gonna take a while for my magic power to regenerate.
Again with the ch?
Ch, you like that?
Ch, ch.
Don't let it get to you.
But it does.
Well then, give me back to Marie.
Unlike someone, I didn't get any extra magic.
Though, if we wait longer, our reunion will be that much more joyous.
Yes.
That's certainly been true in the past.
What's been true in the past?
I'm not talking to you about anything that pertains to Marie.
What?
Why not?
Anyone who approaches Marie is my enemy.
Seriously?
I'm freaking starving here.
Can't you at least use a portal to get us breakfast?
I'm not a delivery service.
Chuh.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
That's a lot of mana.
Mm-hmm.
Hm.
Hmm.
who are they more enemies spatial magic but he's still out cold so how oh man looks like something
didn't go as planned there was a hell of a battle and licked and faulty clearly weren't the winners
cleaning up this mess will be a real pain but still you gotta help out your friends right
that's a unique design well not that it matters this guy moves fast too dark magic dark cloak
lightless slash ow geez now that's literally a pain
well whatever i can heal it up easily enough light magic healing light particles
the same spell this guy can heal too thank you for coming i'm sorry my power alone was not enough to
defeat them you're hurt is it bad i'm fine better now that you're here yes it will be all right
now flame recovery magic phoenix robe
i know you'll succeed where i failed thank you my friends hold on i thought this guy was their leader
see licked trying to do everything on your own is way too much work you insects do you know what
we do to people who harm our friends i'll show you when i'm finished your limbs will be torn from your
body like wings plucked off of a butterfly i detest anybody who hurts licked i hate them
right so who are these people exactly
i'll introduce you these three are the strongest members of the midnight sun
they're the strongest
indeed their power surpasses my own especially when it comes to battle
they are the third eye
and they're more powerful than you so third eye huh
that's impossible stronger than a light mage he's got to be bluffing about that right
we wouldn't bother bluffing such a pain you know
your kingdom takes the clover as its symbol as befits its name let's consider it shall we
each of the clover's leaves supposedly represents one ideal
none of which your kingdom truly embraces they are integrity hope and love such pretty words
these three bear titles with opposite meanings antithetical to integrity we have raya the disloyal
as the antithesis to hope we have veto the despair and as the inverse of love we have fauna the hateful
if someone dares to harm licked i will gladly kill them kill
disloyalty despair and hatred
congratulations those are some real spiffy names you got there
but they don't tell me if you're worth a damn when it comes to a fight
i guess we'll just have to show you then
man how lame
no way
it's just like captain yami's
copy magic dark cloaked lightless slash
your name's raya the disloyal huh swiping spells not cool i'll sue you for copyright infringement
watch out where are you looking beast magic back off
damn it i'm still short on magic
you maggots
he touched it
did he pick up on my key
i can't wait to see the look of despair on your faces when you lose all hope
nothing seasons a meal better than abject misery
hey you
that katana was special order and very expensive
you owe me big
really sir
haven't even finished paying the thing off yet damn it
loathsome
abhorrent
you must die
a salamander
that's spirit magic
spirit magic
does he mean
like you know
hey fond of the hateful isn't it
your personality could use some work
not fully developed yet but still
the spirit of fire
one of the four elements
let's end this
okay
got any final words
you heard our friend
we will repay that pain a hundredfold
you three stay right here
you got me
wait
just a nyami
right
here we go
go on
incinerate him
you're keeping up well
but how much longer can you hold out
just give up
he got hit
keeping us safe is limiting the captain's movement
and i still haven't recovered enough mana to cast my spatial magic
these guys are on a whole other level
sir let me help
no
i told you to stay put
you're not worried about me are you kid
because i'll tell you right now
it's about a billion years too early for that
you just make sure you're watching
things are gonna get serious
it's time to push past my limits
i didn't expect you to be defeated easily
but it will happen
every member of the third eye is stronger than even a magic knight captain
now let's get this over with
kill them
spirit magic
salamander's breath
captain
what the
No. What the...
You're having way too much fun on your own here, Yami.
You should let the rest of us in on it.
So every one of you is stronger than a Magic Knight captain, huh?
We'll see.
Aw, man. Just when I was about to have some kind of awakening, too.
What are you doing here, my high and mighty fellow captains?
I would expect somebody who was in your position to speak with greater care.
You'd better watch your back, foreigner, because I will see you executed one of these days. I swear it.
Jeez, look at your hair. How am I supposed to take you seriously?
Pitiful. You couldn't handle a few measly mages without us.
Come on, cut me some slack, huh?
Amazing. Three of them? Who are they?
You're kidding. They're Magic Knight captains.
Meh.
Aren't you even a little interested?
They aren't Marie, so...
You've really got to work on this little sister thing.
Captain of the Green Praying Mantises, Jack the Ripper, wielder of severing magic.
A super sadist who particularly enjoys tearing things in two.
Apparently, he and Captain Yami flattened a mountain during one of their little spats.
Yeah?
The imposing royal captain of the Silver Eagles, Nozel Silva.
He's got a very commanding presence.
And looks too, damn him.
It's the captain of the Blue Rose Knights! Miss Charlotte Roselay! The cool beauty!
Jeez! What are you so worked up about?
Look at her! She's absolutely gorgeous.
Three captains? This is getting tedious.
Come on. Big deal. Captains or not, they're no match for us.
If someone harms Licht, I will kill them. Kill them. Kill them.
I'm ready to tear someone to pieces. Let's get this party started, shall we?
You're from the Midnight Sun, are you?
There are a great many questions that we would like answers to.
Who are we who is still?
Hmmmm...
Hegumms
It's a huge changes here
What about this event?
egan-in-таки
Okora, Karsizumi
And I know exactly, Once this event wins.
I'dibility to your eyes.
That's all, they may be ending up immediately by Pete Takeout.
Why Jhandsh sorry if you've ever messed up immediately,
brought in this place.
Emily
That's funny.
Chris を nghe
Ah, toki ni tan koku mo ta zaaru koto
Itsu maade kuruisho
You can't stay alive
I want to get back to get back to
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Oh, not yet、になにも、泣いて
obliged to kurish indeed
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
U peer volplexed on camera Im been gain by produced wrote from Postlea
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah when you come on soon
Oh, oh, oh, oh, so, na те
I tried in one day
Быle crazy, bitch.
Over from the dream light!
Sleepy. In spring, it's nice and warm. Good sleeping weather.
In summer, nothing beats a long nap on the beach.
In autumn, the leaves fall. They make a nice bed.
Winter's best, though.
He'd sleep a whole year away if he could.
I have a hard time falling asleep, and I hate anyone who does it easily.
You guys mind? I'm hibernating here.
So sleepy. I am a little more awake now that three magic night captains have shown up, but not much.
Black Clover, page 37. The one with no magic.
That is a thorny young woman.
I'm a little younger man.
Looks like 419,
it's nice and cute.
If you draw my projections and you can see that normally with anything full of an unknown,
the name is 1 to 424 times or 448 days.
I'm a little basedumber in the middle.
Don't forget to ask her questions.
Anything for you at home?
You mind, do not forget to receive your recommendations,
please.
Don't you tin me up.
Don't forget to plug the text.
Don't forget to subscribe to the text.
Don't forget to show!
You'll start this video next week!
Don't forget to add it.
Don't forget to subscribe.
Don't forget to subscribe to the bell!
Don't forget to subscribe!
Don't forget to subscribe